(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-30T02:51:42.744167",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Okay, we reached the destination.
Right on time!
Is everyone ready?
You bet. Let's go.
All right then! Ready...
set...
Jump!
Coming in hot!
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea
endlessly...
Cheerfully...
meeting heart to heart!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah
It's a timeless story with a new feel
not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
that means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far
but we're striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
This is it!
Smashing barriers left and right
That's our myth!
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
It's endless!
So get together, let's reunite!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways,
discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step,
Yeah!
gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation,
a dream unfurls
Let's make friends,
Yeah!
making a moment of history
joyfully!
Follow me;
we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out
over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now;
setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question we'll break through
Don't relent!
We'll keep aspiring to excel
That's our myth!
It's awe-inspiring, going well
Represent!
So light the fire and let's rebel!
The future's brighter, we can tell!
We're ready to...
We're ready to change the world!
Yay!
Uh, uh, uh... Medley, myth medley,
myth medley, myth medley, myth...
What are you doing?
Oh, you too? Both of you guys are
acting a little strange right now.
We're doing crazy faces!
Why are they being so stiff?
We have a show to do!
We have a show to do, come on!
Ina, come on, come on!
Ganbare!
I know the floor is nice, but...
It is really nice.
It's smooth... Ah, sorry! Minasan, thank you
for coming to the show today to celebrate Myth's,
you guessed it, fifth anniversary!
With the medley, a nice throwback.
We've made so many songs together!
Yeah, nostalgic, yeah!
Putting it all together like that,
it's really, like, emotional...
And it's not just like our fifth anniversary,
it's also Hololive English as a whole, five years!
So surreal!
Surreal, oh!
We're old EN!
Yeah, we're old EN!
We also did so much in the last five years,
you know, we had three EN concerts...
Wait, three EN concerts, my word, that's let's go!
Let's go!
And we had a lot of friends join us over the years,
so, you know, in the end I'm really happy
to be performing with you guys. It's so much fun!
Yeah! Yay!
Can't get too emotional just yet though,
because we have a show to do!
Right? Uh-huh.
Yes, anyways, anyways, anyways...
There's a hashtag right here, right here, right here.
Over here, make sure to take lots of pictures,
screenshots, and post them on social media.
Hashtag Myth5Years!
Make us trend!
Trend, get it trending, number one!
If you want... You don't have to if you don't want to.
Just kidding, if you don't do it, we'll be sad,
we'll be angry, we'll get you.
Okay...
Besides that, everybody, this is important.
I'm just checking, making sure
you guys are all here legally. Ta-da!
Did you guys all receive your tickets?
Oh, I remember that.
Ah, it's me! It's me! That's me!
We look so cool.
Yeah, I think I gave you mine at the bar,
it was kind of spicy, remember?
Oh, oh, spicy.
I accosted you on the street, if you remember.
Ah, right! Oh, oh, that's what you were up to!
Yeah, yeah.
I... I might have trespassed.
What? Oya oya?
Why did you do that?
Ina, what did you do?
What did you do?
Who, me?
Hehehe, nice, nice, nice.
Okay...
You know, Ninomae, Ninomae, Ninonis...
What? Sorry. What did you do? You don't want to share?
Nothing! I did nothing illegal!
Fine, don't tell me, keep your secret.
We're used to it, it's been five years.
Now that we know everybody's here with their tickets
and are allowed to be here,
we'll be singing a lot on this stage today,
in different combinations, and different fun songs and so on!
But speaking of the stage...
Oh yeah, look at the stage!
That smooth floor.
Beautiful stage, isn't it?
Gorgeous, stylish.
Fancy! Oh look, that chair, can I sit on it?
How much is that couch? Can I lie on it?
Get your priorities straight.
What about the chandelier, can I swing on it?
Oh my god, the chandelier?
Kiara really liked that one.
Oh, you seen that? Is that a heart?
Oh, did you see that? Is that a heart?
What's the hype for? It's so expensive.
What's the hype for? It looks so expensive.
Did it just change color? I think it just gained some color.
Oh, why, I wonder?
Could it be that it's reacting to everybody's reactions in the chat?
And their... their feelings? It's changing color according to that?
And their... their feelings? Is it changing color according to that?
Are you guys getting excited?
Chat, you guys have an important job to do now, right?
Yes! They are always doing something. You guys are always...
...doing things.
It must be that... it's their power! And their energy! It's flowing through us.
Well, I look forward to seeing how it develops from here on out.
So, you know what you're gonna do, right? You're gonna get out your keyboards and you're gonna type some things.
Wheee! Clack, clack, clack!
Give us your energy!
Give it to us!
Yeah, not that we're trying to shake you down or anything.
I feel it! I'll shake them down. Okay, all right.
We're choosing violence again today. Why are you so violent?
Ina's in a violent mood. She should be wholesome.
I just... I just really have to be here. Five years later...
...she's done! Oh no, they know the real me now.
Sorry, I'm sorry. I feel like I'm always the one who makes things wholesome, so I'll also be wholesome.
I apologize.
Yeah, there's not a lot of time for, for rapping too much today, it would seem.
We're gonna dance our hearts out, sing our hearts out for you guys.
And... oh man, we've been doing a lot of that these days, I think.
I think everybody in Myth deserves a trophy.
A little reward! A little reward! A treat, perhaps?
Cookies. Cookies? Cookies?
Cookies sound good, too. Cookies sound good, too.
Maybe a cookie-shaped tro... oh, or a trophy made out of a cookie.
Or a trophy-shaped cookie. Yes! Yes, please!
You hear that, management?
You better be having some rewards for us.
Please, please! Please, please! Caps Lock demanding!
Yeah, well, that's fine. That's okay, in that case, I know how we can kick this off.
Kick it off?
Yeah. So, it's a little cheesy...
...but I thought maybe the three of us could jump in the air and go, "Woo!", like three, two, one, jump!
And then the camera goes "Vroom!" and we like, fly in the air and go to the next song.
I get it, I get it. I get you.
We want to. Done it before.
Okay, then let's do it! No punching, no violent thoughts, Ina.
Don't punch the camera, I know what you're thinking.
What? Just one... just one upper cut?
Not one, zero! Fine.
Let's do it, okay? Here we go. On my count. Ready?
Next song start! Three...
...two, one, jump!
ビビデバ
[Song: Bibideba]
つまらないデイズもう散々ね! 奇跡願っているだけの人生
Boring days are already over! A life where you're just wishing for miracles
Watch me do... 呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Watch me do... Magic without any tricks or secrets
I wanna be free! だってまだふりだし (The party ain't started)
I wanna be free! Because I'm still at the starting line (The party ain't started)
Heyタクシー ちょっと宇宙迄
Hey taxi, take me to space for a bit
秒針は音を立てて夜を急かす魔物のよう保存
The second hand, like a monster, ticks loudly, urging the night
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Life is a magic that melts away in an instant
それならば駆け抜けて想い通り!保存
If that's the case, then run through it as you wish!
おしゃまに馬車飛び乗って drivin' あたしは大変身メイクアップ!
Jump on the playful carriage and start drivin', I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我儘のまにまに燦きに注意
Be careful not to get caught up in selfishness
洒落た街で dancin'
Dancing in a stylish city
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
If that's the case, goodbye inferiority complex
何時かは喝采クラップオウデエエンス保存
Someday, applause from the audience
皆々御唱和あれ!
Everyone, join in!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa bibbidi bobbidi boowa Yeah
混がらがっても仕様が無い ガラスシューズで踊る Tonight
Even if it's chaotic, there's no other way, dancing in glass shoes tonight
bibbidi bobbidi boowa bibbidi bobbidi boowa Yeah
今夜に明日など無い ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう?
There's no tomorrow tonight, so, those who dance freely win, right?
Dance! ラリラリホ
Dance! la la la li ho
どんな問題も解は一つ
Every problem has only one solution
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す
Love blank papers, correct answers, and mistakes,
本当のあたしの理想
my true ideal.
なんだか世界は限界の気配がして
The world seems to have limits I can feel,
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
just being safe is worrying,
今すぐ jumpin' out
jumpin' out right now!
chitty chitty bang bang chitty bang bang 息だくだくで危機感な日々に
chitty chitty bang bang chitty bang bang, in days when I feel an urgent crisis,
ギリギリ爆発寸前じゃった 今発散してしまおうか
explosive feelings are at their limit, should I let it all out now?
まだまだ BB 弾 巧みに乱射
Still firing away BB pellets skillfully,
一発じゃあ撃ち足りたいわ
one shot is not enough,
遂に導きだした君にアンサー
finally, I found the answer to you,
灰になるまで踊っていよう
dance until it turns to ash!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa bibbidi bobbidi boowa Yeah
混がらがっても仕様が無い ガラスシューズで踊る Tonight
Even if it's chaotic, there's no other way, dancing in glass shoes tonight
bibbidi bobbidi boowa bibbidi bobbidi boowa Yeah
今夜に明日など無い ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう?
There's no tomorrow tonight, so, those who dance freely win, right?
おしゃまに馬車飛び乗って drivin' あたしは大変身メイクアップ!
Jump on the playful carriage and start drivin', I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我儘のまにまに燦きに注意
Be careful not to get caught up in selfishness
洒落た街で dancin'
Dancing in a stylish city
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
If that's the case, goodbye inferiority complex
何時かは喝采クラップオウデエエンス
Someday, applause from the audience
皆々御唱和あれ!
Everyone, join in!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa bibbidi bobbidi boowa Yeah
混がらがっても仕様が無い ガラスシューズで踊る Tonight
Even if it's chaotic, there's no other way, dancing in glass shoes tonight
bibbidi bobbidi boowa bibbidi bobbidi boowa Yeah
今夜に明日など無い ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう?
There's no tomorrow tonight, so, those who dance freely win, right?
勝ち
win...
でしょ
...right?
Hurry.
Let's get started.
Time to get kicking.
Easy peasy, pow.
Hey 頭ン中このクリュー回すのペルソナ
Hey, spinning this crew around in my persona...
に繋がる生まれたてのアイディアとソウルがあるが
...connecting to a freshly born idea and soul.
疑うこともなく才ある者が群がる
Without a doubt, talented people gather.
What about you? 探求妄想膨らます
What about you? Expanding my questing delusions.
いっとまのないを勝ち切るの先に待つ結末は
The ending that awaits beyond winning this breathless game...
麒麟児 大器晩成 臥竜鳳雛の末端
...is a prodigy, a late bloomer, or just the end of a hidden genius.
選ぶのは自分 決起 先に契り
The choice is mine, standing up and sealing the pledge beforehand.
飲めと共に残す生きた証
Drink together and leave behind proof of having lived.
Keep on moving on, on and on.
無我の如くそう瞬間
Ah, that very moment, like selflessness...
時間忘れて耽る on, and on, and no joke
...forgetting time, getting absorbed, on and on and no joke.
Keep it back, coming up, next level. The future's only colored by the cleverest of rebels.
飽和した時代を過去にすべく
To make this saturated era a thing of the past...
狂気孕んだ種が芽吹く いずれ実り昇華 乱れ咲いた桜花浴びるホープ
...the seeds bearing madness sprout, eventually sublimating into a hope showered in cherry blossoms.
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me.
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Can't hide, it's a new generation creation.
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be.
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion.
Too wild, too loud, unbound and unrefined.
Find out that cloud of noise, it's only in our minds.
Right now, it's time. No doubt we're moving on.
I'm drawing my ideal world outside their lines.
思い立ったその瞬間から気付けば今やもう習慣
From the moment I set my mind to it, before I knew it, it became a habit.
Wrecking all expectations, 初心を忘れず耽る on, and on, and no joke
Wrecking all expectations, getting absorbed without forgetting my resolution, on and on and no joke.
腐敗する暇なし 鮮やかな眼差し
No time to rot, with a vibrant gaze...
猛った衝動情熱は依然冷めない
...this raging urge and passion still won't subside.
Never hitting the brakes, to prove I got what it takes. Manifest a world you'll never discern as real or fake, so come on.
Shout it out!
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Just a little madness, you can't take the drive outta me.
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Can't hide, it's a new generation creation.
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Tearing up the canvas, won't be what you want me to be.
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Can't fight this uprising outbreak of passion.
人様に誇れずとも自分の背中押せるような夢があればそれでいい
Even if it's nothing to brag about, as long as there's a dream that pushes me forward, that's enough.
たられば終わるよりも只管にもがく 止まない雨はないと信じ今に様変わる
Rather than ending with 'what-ifs', I'll just struggle endlessly, believing no storm lasts forever.
Words like "gifted", "prolific", you better be specific.
Broad strokes, blowing smoke, blink and you could miss it.
These words illicit visions of a future so exquisite, some masterpiece you've never seen, awaiting the few committed.
知らないことがあれば研究
If there's something I don't know, I'll research it.
出来ないことがあれば練習 姿勢は前のめりゆえの熱中
If there's something I can't do, I'll practice. Leaning forward in absolute obsession.
成功の真反対にある失敗が一番の近道だ
Failure, which is the complete opposite of success, is actually the shortest path.
You can do it さあ行こう 時は満ちた
You can do it, let's go. The time has come.
It's about time.
Stars aligning, all designing, I'm already on my way.
迸る音が歪み昂る体内中満ちるまで
Until the surging sounds distort and completely fill my rising body...
And if it's lost, I'll find it, all this blind resolve, gotta go it my own way.
Vicious and vivid and striking, my 熱狂
Vicious and vivid and striking, my passionate excitement!
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
Vicious and vivid and striking, my 熱狂
Vicious and vivid and striking, my passionate excitement!
熱狂
Passionate excitement!
誤解すんなよ こんな滑稽な
Don't misunderstand, it's laughable,
サッと過ぎ去る毎日
how time flashes by every day.
Another prisoner of fate no one could fake out.
Stay awake now, you know you wanna fire away.
Now there's no question where the fault lies.
These days I struggle just to empathize.
もう戻らないって分かっているんだろう
There's no going back, and you know that.
Cast a blessing on my cursed role
And feed this bleeding egotistical soul
Before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
嗚呼 美しい蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
身分不相応の嫉妬に塗れた
Dripping in jealousy that's a bit too daring
ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
An ecstasy that's just a little bit lacking
誤解も解けないまま私 人を傷つけて
I hurt somebody without ever opening my eyes
一粒の才すら無いわ
But there's no talent here, it's clear to see
転がり落ちたシゴロサイ
The rigged dice falls and rolls
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I ever notice your love and affection
Cast a blessing on my cursed heart
Why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか神様 教えてくれますか
Pray tell me, God
Pray tell me, God...
言葉少なに 貴方に捧ぐ
I give to you silently
今に消えてしまいそうなこの命を
My life that's about to burn out
鳴呼 愛おしい セピア色した
Ah, and these sepia-toned sights
何より大事なこの景色を
they're most precious of all
もう少し見ていたいよな
I wish I could see them a bit more...
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
If I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
Everything I ever wanted was in front of me
The devils on my shoulder never let me be
Obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
Somebody save me
My world is caving in coz I thought I deserved it all for free
遠き日の 夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
鳴呼 美しい 蒼い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into my mind
もう少し強くならないとな
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
はらり はられ
Fluttering and falling
今 踊り 踊れ
Now, dance and dance!
恋焦がれ 遊べ さぁ
Yearning with love, come play now
喰らって 唄え
Consume it all and sing!
花に 紛れ
Lost among the flowers,
今 を 取り戻せ
reclaim this very moment!
粋狂 に 遊べ さぁ
Play whimsically, come now,
ここ で 踊れ
and dance right here!
ひゅるりらぱっぱ
[Title: Hyururirapappa]
ひふみよご
One, two, three, four, five
あっ ちゅー 間 時 が 過ぎ て く
In the blink of an eye, time flies by
選り取り 見取り さぁ 祭り囃子
Take your pick, the festival music plays
あれもこれも籠 放り込み
Throwing everything into the basket,
欲に塗れ生きていたい
I want to live covered in desire
人生 寄り道 回り道
Life has detours and roundabout ways
生きたいように生きなはれや
Live it exactly how you want to!
はらり はられ
Fluttering and falling
今 踊り 踊れ
Now, dance and dance!
恋焦がれ 遊べ さぁ
Yearning with love, come play now
喰らって 唄え
Consume it all and sing!
花に 紛れ
Lost among the flowers,
今 を 取り戻せ
reclaim this very moment!
粋狂 に 遊べ さぁ
Play whimsically, come now,
ここ で 踊れ
and dance right here!
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり ら ぱっぱ
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururira-pappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり らっぱー
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururirappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり ら ぱっぱ
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururira-pappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり らっぱー
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururirappa
ちりぬるを
Even the blooming flowers scatter
あっ ちゅー 間 時 は 過ぎ
In the blink of an eye, time has passed
さぁ 酸いも甘いも祭り囃子
Now, sour or sweet, the festival music plays
味わい尽くしてしまいましょう
Let's savor it all to the very end
さぁ 何から平らげよう
Now, what shall we devour first?
人生 気付けば 矢の如し
Life, before you know it, is like an arrow
命の花を打ち上げましょう
Let's set off the fireworks of our lives
はらり はられ
Fluttering and falling
今 踊り 踊れ
Now, dance and dance!
恋焦がれ 遊べ さぁ
Yearning with love, come play now
喰らって 唄え
Consume it all and sing!
花に 紛れ
Lost among the flowers,
今 を 取り戻せ
reclaim this very moment!
粋狂 に 遊べ さぁ
Play whimsically, come now,
ここ で 踊れ
and dance right here!
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり ら ぱっぱ
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururira-pappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり らっぱー
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururirappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり ら ぱっぱ
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururira-pappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり らっぱー
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururirappa
花 よ 花 よ 誇り なさい
Flower, oh flower, stand proud
まごう こと なく 君 の まま
Without a doubt, just as you are
上 を 向い て ご覧 なさい
Look up and see
最後 の 日 まで 花 で あれ
Be a flower until your very last day
はらり はられ
Fluttering and falling
今 踊り 踊れ
Now, dance and dance!
誰 彼 も 遊べ さぁ
Everyone and anyone, come play now
喰らって 唄え
Consume it all and sing!
離れ離れ
Though we may be far apart,
demo 花火 上げて
let's still set off fireworks!
粋狂 に 遊べ さぁ
Play whimsically, come now,
ここ で 踊れ
and dance right here!
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり ら ぱっぱ
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururira-pappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり らっぱー
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururirappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり ら ぱっぱ
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururira-pappa
ひゅる ひゅるりー ら ら ひゅるり らっぱー
Hyuru-hyururi-ra-ra, hyururirappa
あしたしたい？ こうしたい？ どうしたい？ まるで死んでるみたい
Want to do this tomorrow? Want to do this? What do you want to do? It's like being dead.
石の上にも三年 でもそんなんじゃ エーアイサーキュレーション
Three years on a cold stone... but that's not enough for an AI circulation.
今日やっと始まるストーリー 生まれたての卵のような イン・モーション
Today, our story finally begins, like a newly hatched egg in motion.
殻から飛び出し いい気味だなんて
Jumping out of the shell, you say "serves you right"
君は決め顔で せーのっ
with a smug look on your face. Ready, set, go!
永遠を願った夢に
To the dream where we wished for eternity...
終わりを告げる朝が来て
...the morning comes to announce its end.
お砂糖でできたその涙
Those tears made of sugar...
見つめ 見つめ 見つけた心
...I stared and stared at them, and found my heart.
甘く ほろ苦い カラメルのように
Sweet and bittersweet, like caramel,
絡まるリボンは 呪いの鎧だけど
the tangled ribbons are like a cursed armor, but...
この気持ちはそう
...these feelings, yes...
この気持ちにしか
...only with these feelings...
きっとわかんないから
...will we surely understand.
君と 手と手繋いで
Hand in hand with you,
一つ 一つ、叶えてゆこう
let's make each and every dream come true.
僕らの物語は 今日も続く、約束
Our story continues even today, a promise.
色とりどりの 真っ黒な歴史
A colorful, pitch-black history...
愛おしい私の歴史
...my precious history.
誰も知らない 真っ白なページ
A blank page that nobody knows...
更新してゆく
...I'll keep on updating it.
あの 一紡ぎの ほころびは
The tear of that single spun thread...
話したくない 喜びで
...is filled with a joy I don't want to let go of.
つぎはぎ だらけの この心
This heart covered in patches...
紡ぎ 紡ぎ 繋いだところ
...is where we spun and spun to connect.
あこがれ 恋い焦がれ 待ち焦がれ 全部全部全部全部全部！
Yearning, longing, waiting impatiently... all of it, all of it!
プリンみたいに ひっくり返して カラメル カラメル 内緒のフレーバー！
Flip it over like pudding! Caramel, caramel, a secret flavor!
動きたい？ ここにいたい？ 切り離したままじゃ僕らは外れるピース
Want to move? Want to stay here? If we remain separated, we're pieces that won't fit.
でもそんなんじゃやだ！ おいで、決め顔でせーのっ！
But I don't want that! Come on, make a smug face, ready, set, go!
숨겨놓은 치트키는 직접 골라보는
The hidden cheat key is chosen by myself.
운명의 붉은 리본을 바짝 끌어당겨서
Pulling the red string of fate tight towards me.
この気持ちはそう
These feelings, yes...
この気持ちにしか
...only with these feelings...
きっとわかんないから
...will we surely understand.
君と 手と手繋いで
Hand in hand with you,
一つ 一つ、叶えてゆこう
let's make each and every dream come true.
僕らの物語は 今日も続く、約束
Our story continues even today, a promise.
君と 手と手繋いで
Hand in hand with you,
一つ 一つ、叶えてゆこう
let's make each and every dream come true.
僕らの物語は 今日も続く、約束
Our story continues even today, a promise.
色とりどりに 真っ黒な歴史
A colorful, pitch-black history...
愛おしい僕らの歴史
...our precious history.
残さず食べて
Eat it all up,
全部糧にして
turn it all into nourishment,
更新してゆく
and keep on updating.
Yeah!
What... what are we doing?
Welcome back, Calli!
Oh, hi! Hey.
You guys look a little tired.
I thought we were posing for the Myth album cover, which is not coming out, by the way.
Oh, no, no.
Don't misunderstand! Don't misunderstand.
Well, we have a mixtape, but...
Someday, someday.
Did you guys enjoy the song so far?
What did you think?
Yeah.
Was it really hard?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
With a really cute part from Ina!
Yeah!
Caramel ribbon cursetard.
Yeah, you guys's voices... you guys's? Your voices fit really, really well with it.
Oh, thank you!
Yeah, it's a really cute song.
Yeah. Me and Ina were like, "What song should we do together?"
And I was like, "Huh, I wonder if Ina would let us do a Monogatari song?"
So I was like, "Monogatari, please!" And she's like, "Okay!"
Wait, you're talking to Ni-no-ma-e I-na-'nis, of course she's going to say yes.
Yeah, of course I'm going to say yes.
But we all like Monogatari, right?
We do, yeah. Kiara, you could have done it too, huh?
Sure, yeah, I would have.
We could have had her doing the...
(humming)
Now I want to see that.
I can do it. I can do it now.
Ah, she should have done it as a three-peat!
And kind of more cute.
But also, I tried to make it as cute as I can.
What about your solos, though?
Yeah! Except mine is not yet.
We don't know yours yet, though.
You guys know I could rap that fast?
We were also surprised!
Kind of crazy.
Impressive.
Yeah, ma-ma, ma-ma.
Cool, Calli!
I did my best. It was like enough, enough, it was like, "Oh yeah, she did it." And plus, the dancing was pretty cool, so.
Oh yeah. I'm honored.
Good job.
And Ina too, very impressive!
I really challenged myself.
The dancing has leveled up so much!
Yeah!
Cute, beautiful.
Beautiful.
Demure.
It was a lot of fun. It was difficult, of course. My heart rate shot through the roof, but...
...we did it. I think. We did it.
And then me and Ina did some air guitar.
Yeah. Oh, my original song, Sepia. A very close song to my heart. Thank you guys.
They made guitar, by the way.
Yeah, yeah, I loved the purple guitar. So cute.
Well, what's still missing now?
Oh, there are a couple of songs missing, aren't there?
Like Wawa's solo.
My solo. A lot of, a lot of...
And mine and Calli's combination song.
I wonder, what you guys are going to see.
I wonder. I wonder, I wonder.
I will just say that the song for me and Calli was also chosen, kind of suggested by me. Thank you, Calli!
You're welcome!
Thank you for being okay with it.
That's a nice song, I guess. Yeah, I don't want to spoil anything, but it was pretty good. Yes.
And my solo will be... epic and hype. So please look forward to it.
Why did you choose it? Can you give a hint? Can you give a hint? I know it's about to happen pretty soon here, but...
Eh! No hints! No, that's it!
Okay, alright, alright.
Why? I'm a toddler, why?
Yes, we still have a lot of our show left over, so don't tune out. There is lots more.
Stay with us! Stay right here! Don't move.
Wait! And continue to watch until the end.
And use the hashtag, don't forget that. Okay, hashtag.
Are you ready to move on? Move on! Move on! Okay.
What should we do? No. What should we...
We should play with the camera. What do you want to do, Ina? What do you want to do the most?
I know what to do. Oh! Oh!
What are you going to do?
Nothing violent, right?
Not something... Uh-oh, she's gonna do something violent.
She's gonna do something violent. Yeah!
Hey!
Dear God, I've come to repent my sins
Let your blood wash me clean, for I'm...
I'm...
I'm a rotten girl.
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
The temptation flowing through my veins
I'm bounded by these shackles of shame
I promised I'd indulge no more
But my heart I can't ignore
In my dreams, they're turning up the heat
I'm a dirty, rotten girl
On lock, underneath the bleachers
Just watch, look beyond the smoke and mirrors
Heart-struck? Shun the non-believer
Our operation would never be complete
Red-hot, tension with each whisper
Snapshot, quiet moans and muffled whimpers
Come on, can't you feel the fever
Rising up, rising up to the sky?
As testaments echo, fear ignites beneath my skin
The lord sayeth, "Halt, thy child, don't give in to sin"
It's driving me crazy, the urge to forsake thee
Yet, something shifts within this wicked bliss
I swore I'd never sin again
But my patience's running thin
Student council breathing down my neck
I wonder if they're hiding from me
Forbidden fruits before my eyes
And a taste that's so divine
My regrets rewriting history
I'm a sad, pathetic girl
Someone, please, tell me what to do
Because, honestly, I just can't stop!
I've been trying so hard and I can't stop!
What would god think?
And I, I know I'm supposed to be a good girl but...
Somehow, I just can't control myself!
Every time I see them, touching skin to skin
My mind goes, my mind goes, ah!
Could Eve be our idol? Could she lead us through the light?
We'd all be disciples of her lemon-driven bite
Can somebody save me? The urge to forsake thee
Still, something shifts within this wicked bliss
The power resting in my hands
For my god has other plans
In salvation, I can live my life
As an ordinary girl
I can't resist it anymore
'Cause I smell slow burn galore
All the trauma from a cobblestone
Could never beat the devil in me
An honest sinner 'til I die
What's the harm if i don't mind?
With the paddle that empowers me
I can live a sinful life
チェックワンツー！
Check, one, two!
チェックワンツー！イェー！
Check, one, two! Yeah!
あーもう無理！文化祭
Ah, I can't take it anymore! The school festival...
言葉にダンスに... キャパオーバーです
with words and dancing... my capacity is overloaded.
心配無用の おまじない
No need to worry, here's a magic spell.
きっと報われる その努力
Your efforts will surely be rewarded.
「笑顔になあれ」
"May you smile!"
ドキドキしてる
My heart is pounding...
ありえないくらい本気だし
because I'm unbelievably serious.
まほうがかかる
A magic spell is cast...
今日限り ヒーロータイム
for today only, it's hero time!
何とぞね？
Please, okay?
Let's go!
baby kiss 照れないで
Baby kiss, don't be shy.
気持ち伝えてよ！
Express your feelings to me!
(好き) 好き？
(I love you) You love me?
相思相愛 好き
We're mutually in love, I love you!
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup gets ruined,
髪が乱れても
even if my hair gets messy...
(好き！) 好き？
(I love you!) You love me?
絶対忘れない
I'll never forget...
青春の1ページ
this page of our youth!
あー超気持ちー！文化祭
Ah, this feels so amazing! The school festival...
隣で笑ってる 君のおかげだ
is all thanks to you smiling next to me.
弱気な私 変えてくれた
You changed my timid self.
絶対最強のパートナー
You're my absolute strongest partner.
マジでありがとう
Thank you so much, seriously.
カクセイしてる
I've been awakened...
ファンサの効力 マシマシで
with the power of fan service fully maxed out!
まほうつよまる
The magic is growing stronger...
終わりかけ ヒーロータイム
as our hero time is coming to an end.
延長、ね？
An extension, okay?
Let's go!
baby kiss 隠さずに
Baby kiss, without hiding it.
気持ち伝えてよ！
Express your feelings to me!
(好き) 好き？
(I love you) You love me?
相思相愛 好き
We're mutually in love, I love you!
おやつ食べたいし
I want to eat some snacks,
帰宅いいですか？
so can I please go home?
(ダメ！) ダメ？
(No!) No?
ごめんうそ嘘
Sorry, just kidding!
こちらこそ帰さない
On the contrary, I won't let you go!
TakaMori for five years!
Can you guys keep it going?
いくよー！
Here we go!
かりちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Cali-chan super cute?
(かりちゃんは超かわいい！)
(Cali-chan is super cute!)
きあらちゃんは超かわいい？
Is Kiara-chan super cute?
(きあらちゃんは超かわいい！)
(Kiara-chan is super cute!)
Big ups, everybody!
Danke schön!
Thank you very much!
Are you ready?
3, 2, 1, Go!
まほう解けちゃうね...
The magic is about to wear off...
最後に聞かせてよ
Let me hear it one last time.
好き？
Do you love me?
大きな声で
Say it out loud...
好き！
"I love you!"
メイク崩れても
Even if my makeup gets ruined,
髪が乱れても
even if my hair gets messy...
好き！
I love you!
好き？
You love me?
絶対忘れない
I'll never forget...
青春の1ページ
this page of our youth!
な×7 Yeah!
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na, Yeah!
ダンダンダン ダンダンダン ダンダンダン ダンダンダン
Dandadan dandadan dandadan dandadan
歯車が回りだすからアンタの
Since the gears are starting to turn,
中じゃ足りなくなってかなわん
you aren't enough on your own to handle it.
クワバラ クワバラ クワバラ
Kuwabara, kuwabara, kuwabara!
目にも留まらぬ速さ
At a speed invisible to the naked eye.
くたばらん 黙らん 下がらん
I won't die, won't shut up, won't back down,
押し通すわがまま
pushing through my selfishness!
そこどきな 邪魔だ
Get out of the way, you're in the way!
私はもう一人のあなた
I am the other you!
サダちゃん カヤちゃん
Sada-chan, Kaya-chan...
「Wonderland」
...Wonderland!
ご祈祷中に何だが 4時44分回ったら
Sorry to interrupt your prayers, but once it's past 4:44...
4尺4寸4分様が 降臨(カミナッチャ) Bang around
The 4-shaku 4-sun 4-bun ghost descends to bang around!
呼ぶ声がしたんなら 文字通りお疲れ様やん
If you heard a voice calling you, you're literally done for.
入れ入れた 入れ入れた 入れ入れた
I'm inside, I'm inside, I'm inside, I'm inside, I'm inside...
必死で這い出た先で霧は晴れた
After desperately crawling out, the fog cleared.
でことぼこがうまく噛み合ったら
If our uneven edges fit perfectly together,
痛みが重なったら
when our pain overlaps...
ココロ カラダ アタマ みなぎってゆく なんだか
My heart, body, and mind are somehow surging with energy,
背中にいま羽が生えたならば
and if wings were to sprout on my back right now...
闇からおさらば
Farewell to the darkness!
飛び立ってゆく彼方
Flying away to the other side!
ココロ カラダ アタマ 懐かしい温かさ
My heart, body, and mind feel a nostalgic warmth,
足元にいま花が咲いたならば
and if a flower were to bloom at my feet right now...
闇からおさらば
Farewell to the darkness!
飛び立ってゆく彼方
Flying away to the other side!
何度だって生きる おまえや君の中
I will live again and again, inside you and you,
まぶたの裏や耳の中
behind your eyelids and in your ears,
胸の奥に息づいてるメロディ リズムに
to the melody and rhythm still breathing deep inside your chest.
今日も賽の河原ど真ん中
Today too, right in the middle of the riverbank of death,
積み上げてく Top of the top
piling it up to the top of the top.
鬼とチャンバラ The lyrical chainsaw massacre
Sword fighting with demons—the lyrical chainsaw massacre!
渡る大波乱 花を咲かし シャララ
Crossing great turbulence, making flowers bloom, sha-la-la!
払いたいのなら末代までの札束
If you want to exorcise it, bring a stack of cash that'll last generations.
誰が開けたかパンドラ あとは何があっても知らんがな
Who opened Pandora's box? I don't care what happens after this!
何百年待ったか 超久しぶりの娑婆だ
How many hundreds of years have I waited? It's been ages since I was in the mortal world!
ガキや若葉まだこっち来んじゃねえよ馬鹿が
You kids and greenhorns, don't come over here yet, you idiots!
いま確かに目が合ったな こういうことかよシャマラン
We definitely made eye contact just now. Is this what you meant, Shyamalan?
入れ入れた 入れ入れた 入れ入れた
I'm inside, I'm inside, I'm inside, I'm inside, I'm inside...
眠り飽きた先でキミが待ってた
After getting tired of sleeping, you were there waiting for me.
盾と矛が肩を抱き合ったら
When the shield and the spear put their arms around each other,
怒りが消え去ったら
when the anger completely fades away...
ココロ カラダ アタマ みなぎってゆく なんだか
My heart, body, and mind are somehow surging with energy,
背中にいま羽が生えたならば
and if wings were to sprout on my back right now...
闇からおさらば
Farewell to the darkness!
飛び立ってゆく彼方
Flying away to the other side!
ココロ カラダ アタマ 懐かしい温かさ
My heart, body, and mind feel a nostalgic warmth,
足元にいま花が咲いたならば
and if a flower were to bloom at my feet right now...
闇からおさらば
Farewell to the darkness!
飛び立ってゆく彼方
Flying away to the other side!
何度だって生きる おまえや君の中
I will live again and again, inside you and you,
まぶたの裏や耳の中
behind your eyelids and in your ears,
胸の奥に息づいてるメロディ リズムに
to the melody and rhythm still breathing deep inside your chest.
Fortune Spinner
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the Muses whisper "truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead:
A wild chase,
a frantic pace
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
Ah... la da da da da da
I'm always spinning fate
Whoah yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet,
I spin back 'round with every chance I get
The wheel turns and the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead!
A perfect chance,
a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
Ooh la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoah, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
New song, new song, new song!
やったー！
Yay!
Yay, it's our first song as a trio, you guys!
We did it! Oh, it's true!
It was over a little fast.
あ、そう、今考えてみると…
Ah, so, now that I'm thinking about it...
2分くらいしかなかったよね
Yeah, it was only like two minutes.
いい運動になったね
That was a workout.
今の若い子は「短いのがいい」って言うからかな？
I guess it's because all the zoomers are like, "it's short nowadays", huh?
みんなそう言ってるよね
That's what everybody says.
私は違うけど / 私もね
Not me! / Certainly not.
でも、残念ながらこれが今回のライブ最後の曲でした！
But yeah, unfortunately, this was also the last song for this live!
ええー…
Aww...
でも！私たちの5周年記念楽曲…
But! Yeah, but the music video...
『Fortune Spinner』のミュージックビデオが
for our 5th anniversary song, "Fortune Spinner",
このライブのすぐ後にホロライブEnglish公式YouTubeチャンネルでプレミア公開されます！
will premiere on the Hololive English official YouTube channel right after this concert,
だからみんな、残っててね？
so make sure you stick around, okay?
見逃さないでね！ / たくさん見てね！
Don't miss it! / Make sure you watch it a lot!
何回もループしてね！
And loop it a lot!
イェーイ！ / そうだね！
Yeah! / Right!
そうですね、そうですね
Soudesu ne, soudesu ne.
まだお祝いすることは残ってるよね？
We still have some celebrating to do, though, right?
そう！最後だから、ここで自分たちをお祝いする時間だと思う！5周年！
That's right! I think it's time, because it's the end, that we kind of celebrate ourselves here. Five years!
準備はいい？ / うん！
Are we ready for that? / Yes!
準備万端！よし、やろう！やろう！
Yes, we're ready! Okay, let's do it! Let's do it!
おや？あそこにあるケーキは何？
Oh? What is that cake over there?
私のじゃないよ / ええー…
That is not mine. / Oh, come on...
イナ、イナ、イナ、気をつけて！
Ina, Ina, Ina, be careful!
どれだけ美味しそうか話そうよ！
Let's talk about how delicious it looks!
ほとんどイナより大きいね
It's almost bigger than Ina!
ちょっと待って、今はダメ！
Hey, stop, stop, stop! Not now, not now!
イチゴを取らないで！
Hey, don't take off the strawberries!
落ち着いて。後でお祝いして食べよう。後で、後で。
Hold your horses. Let's eat it later and celebrate. Later, later.
見て、トロフィーがあるよ！ / 本当だ！
And look, there's trophies! / Yeah, there are!
授賞式ができるね？ / やろう！
We can do an award show, right? / Oh, let's do that!
本当にトロフィーを用意してくれたの？
Did they actually get us trophies?
うん、話を聞いてくれてたんだね。ありがとう！
Yeah! They were listening. Thank you!
5年だもん、賞をもらう価値はあるよね
Five years, we deserve an award.
有意義な成果がたくさんあるから、何があるか見てみよう！
We have so many meaningful accomplishments, so let's see what they all are, okay?
オッケー！何だろう？
Okay! What'll it be?
私から始めようか？私のもらうね。 / ハクション！
Shall I start? I'll take mine. / (sneezes) Achoo!
お大事に！ / お大事にね。
Bless you! / Bless you.
タララーン！ / ハクション！
Tada-da-da-da! / (sneezes) Achoo!
お大事に！授賞式を邪魔するつもりはないんだよ。 / 何をもらったの？
Oh, bless you! We're not trying to disrupt your award ceremony. / What did you get?
私の賞は…ええと、こう書いてあるかな…
Alright, my award is... let's see... I think it says...
最多調理賞！
Most Meals Cooked Award!
彼女は料理してる！ / ホロENでね！
She's cooking! / In HoloEN!
料理させてあげて！ / たくさん料理してるもんね。
Let her cook! / She has been cooking a lot.
たくさん作ってるよ。
She made a lot.
ありがとう。主に健康的な生活を送って、
Yes, thank you. I think that's what that's about mostly, about, you know, me living a healthy lifestyle
家でたくさん料理をしたことについてだね。
and then cooking many meals at home, yeah.
いつかみんなにも料理を振る舞えたらいいな。
I wish I could cook for you girls someday.
今日のパフォーマンスを楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
I hope you guys enjoyed my performances today. I am so proud
何年も経った今でも、同期と一緒にここに立てることを誇りに思います。
to stand here with my genmates, even on this day after so many years.
もちろん、これからも努力し続けます。もっと賞をもらえるようにね。
Um, I will continue to work hard, of course, so that I can maybe gather even more awards.
これは家の棚に飾るよ。猫たちが毛をいっぱいつけたり、
Um, I will put this on my shelf at home where my cats will also probably put a lot of fur on it,
落としたりするだろうけど。 / 落としたりね。
or knock it down. / Or knock it down.
やめてよ！ / 猫はそういうの好きだからね。 / 本物のガラス？
Oh, no, no, no! / They like to do that. / Is it out of real glass?
結構重いね。 / 少し気をつけなきゃ。
It's kind of heavy. / I've got to be a little bit careful.
みんな本当にありがとう！大好きだよ。これまで光栄でした。
Thank you guys so much! I love you girls. It's been an honor so far,
これからも一緒に頑張ろうね。
so let's do our best together.
この賞をありがとう！
Thank you for this award!
次は誰？ / 次は誰？一伊那尓栖かな？
Who is next? / Who is next? Is it Ninomae Ina'nis?
私？私の賞は…何だろう。
Me? Oh, could my award be... let's see.
誰が暴力的？ / そう、誰が暴力的？
Who's violent? / Yeah, who's violent?
何の暴力？ / 自業自得だよ。 / 違うよ！よし…
Violent what? / You do it to yourself. / No, no, no. All right...
私の賞は…
My award is...
おお、やっぱり… / もう予想してたよ！
Oh, yes... / I already guessed!
「最も床で過ごした時間が多いで賞」！
"Most Time Spent on the Floor Award!"
それは納得だね！ / おめでとう！
Oh, that I believe, yeah! / Yes! Congratulations!
ありがとう、みんな。私がこの賞をもらうなんて思ってなかったかもしれないけど、
Thank you, thank you, thank you. I know you guys probably think I would never get this award, but, you know...
床にいるために一生懸命頑張ったんだよ！ / 素晴らしいね。
I worked so hard to stay on the floor! / Very, very impressive.
それに、床にいただけじゃなくて、
And, uh, yeah, not only did I stay on the floor, I, you know,
今年はみんなとうまくパフォーマンスできるように、
really did my best to practice dancing and singing this year
歌とダンスを本当に頑張って練習したんだ。
to perform well with you guys, and I hope that you guys see that as well.
応援本当にありがとう。これからもこのメンバーで頑張るね。
Thank you so much for all your support. I'll continue to do my best with these girls.
イェーイ！これからも頑張ろう！ありがとう、イナ！
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Let's keep doing it! Thank you, Ina!
そして最後は…
And last, but not least...
森さん！何だろう？
Mori, Mori! Oh, what could it be?
クシャミ王。最多クシャミ賞。
Our sneezer. The most sneezer.
5周年記念配信で最もクシャミをしたで賞。 / 祝福されてるね。
The most sneezes in the 5th anniversary showcase. / Most blessed.
実は、私のトロフィーは…「最良の最悪運賞」！
Okay. Well, actually, my trophy is for... Best Worst Luck Award!
特に課金要素のあるゲームにおいてね。
Especially in games where there are microtransactions.
現実でもそれを見たことがあるよ。
Yeah, I mean, I've seen it happen in real life.
リアルタイムでね！
Real life, real time!
でも、サインカードを引くための執念と決意は…
But the dedication, the determination to pull a signed card or not...
まだ諦めないよ！
I'm not gonna give up yet.
すぐに幸せになれると思う…
Real quick, I'm gonna be very happy...
このセリフがすごく好きなんだ、諦めないって…
I really like that line. I'm not gonna...
give up, yeah, because, because
I'd like to think that we're not gonna give up yet
because there's still so much that I want to do,
the three of us together,
together, you know?
And I didn't think that I would be here five years from the start with you guys.
Same. / Same.
I really thought I'd be out of here. / Same.
But now, I can't... I can't see a future where I'm not here with you guys, so for now...
Aww, so sweet!
Shucks! / Okay.
So because of that, I'm not gonna give up... I don't want to give up yet. So let's do our best!
Do our best! Do our best! Do our best!
Oh yeah, the wrap-up music is playing!
The wrap-up music is playing! I'm just gonna start talking about nothing
because that annoys me when they play the jingle that tells us to go. This morning I ate a bagel...
and it had cream cheese on it. It was delicious, but it went all over my face
and I got into big, big trouble with my trainer. / You're a rapper, you should wrap!
Anyway, you can't get rid of me!
You can't get rid of...
...any of us, hopefully! / Any of us.
All right, everybody. All good things come to an end, unfortunately.
But thank you so much to the Hololive community for supporting us continuously for five years.
Thank you to the girlies today and all the staff-san that supported us also
for the celebration, who gave us the trophies. / Yeah.
Once again, congratulations to us! To us!
Yay!
Oh, five years! Oh yeah!
Thank you!
Thanks, guys!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Peace.
Next is the merch! / Merch! Merch, please! Merch is next!
The merchant-eyes! / The merchandise!
Next is the merchandise announcement!
We have Hololive English -Myth- 5th Anniversary Celebration merch being released!
Let's look at the details. Check it out!
First up, we've got the Mirror Acrylic Panel.
It's designed so that the surroundings and background of the illustration have a metallic, mirrored vibe.
Ooh, so cool! I absolutely love this illustration. Hope you guys do too!
Next up, we have the Collection Cards.
These cards feature a shiny metallic finish...
...and you can choose from three different designs.
Also, the backside is matching for us all.
Make sure to get the one from your oshi, for sure!
Next up, we have the Coin Medals!
Our shiny 5th Anniversary commemorative Coin Medals.
There's one design for each member...
...and the backside also has a common design.
They come in an antique gold-plated finish inside...
...the original packaging. Ooh, so shiny!
Oh man, everything looks so good! But I'm especially interested in what we have to show you guys next.
Next up, we have the Anniversary Hats!
So first up, Anniversary Hat - Mori Calliope.
This one uses a soft, fluffy fabric.
The Death Sensei part is removable, so you can also rock it without him.
Make sure that you check it out. It's super stylish!
I love the shape so much, and...
...all of my member Dead Beats voted on it together, so hope that you guys will enjoy.
Next up, we have mine, the Anniversary Hat from Takanashi Kiara!
It looks like this.
The decorative parts are removable.
It can be worn reversibly, inside out, so you'll have a different color then.
And it's a bucket hat style design, which we didn't have before for me.
Very fashionable, I must say!
Last but not least, we have my hat, the Anniversary Hat - Ninomae Ina'nis!
The ribbon part is removable, and the patches are super cute too!
You can wear it to become Takodachi. Yes.
And yeah, you can mix and match with or without the ribbon for different looks.
So everybody, be sure to check our merch out!
And that concludes our 5th Year Anniversary stream!
Ultimate Myth!
I'm not gonna give up yet,
I spin back 'round with every chance I get,
The wheel turns and the die is cast,
The time has come for fate to change at last.
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead!
A perfect chance, a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
Ooh la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoah, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead